export const arrayOfQuiz = [
  {
    question: "Whose standard is ES-262?",
    choices: ["HTML", "Ruby", "Kotlin", "JavaScript"],
    correctChoice: "JavaScript",
  },
  {
    question: "What does &nbsp; does in an HTML page?",
    choices: ["Adds space(s)", "Adds link break", "Adds comma", "Does Nothing"],
    correctChoice: "Adds space(s)",
  },
  {
    question: "What is not a value of the property 'position'?",
    choices: ["absolute", "fixed", "jiggly", "relative"],
    correctChoice: "jiggly",
  },
  {
    question: "What is best for creating responsive sites?",
    choices: ["Float", "Flexbox", "Margin", "Padding"],
    correctChoice: "Flexbox",
  },
  {
    question: "What is called 'sibling selector' in CSS?",
    choices: [".", "+", ">", "~"],
    correctChoice: "+",
  },
  {
    question:
      "If a local and global variable have the same name, which one will be used inside the function?",
    choices: ["Local", "Global", "Both", "None"],
    correctChoice: "Local",
  },
  {
    question: "What are arrays in JavaScript??",
    choices: ["Arrays", "Square Brackets", "Containers", "Objects"],
    correctChoice: "Objects",
  },
  {
    question: "What does ECMA stand for?",
    choices: [
      "Every Convenience Made Available",
      "European Computer Manufacturers Association",
      "England China Malaysia America?",
      "It means nothing",
    ],
    correctChoice: "European Computer Manufacturers Association",
  },
  {
    question: "What is localStorage() used for?",
    choices: [
      "To store data in system memory",
      "To store data in browser",
      "Same as sessionStorage()",
      "To store data in browser without an expiry time",
    ],
    correctChoice: "To store data in browser without an expiry time",
  },
  {
    question: "Can clearInterval() be used inside setInterval()?",
    choices: ["Yes", "No", "Sometimes", "Who cares?"],
    correctChoice: "Yes",
  },
];
